CARLOS MANUEL ALCANTARA RODRIGUEZ

Jr. Front-end web Developer

PROFILE

Junior front-end developer on a journey to bridge technology with user satisfaction. Currently pursuing a degree in computer engineering, I bring a diverse background that includes customer service and IT service desk experience, along with a stint as a supervisor.

CONTACT

+525529412499

carlos.ma.rodriguez91@outlook.com

Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Credit and Collections advocate, AT&T

DECEMBER 2017 - MAY 2018

Equipped me with essential skills for the software development field. Thriving in a fast-paced environment, I have mastered multitasking and problem-solving. Thanks to these approaches make me an asset to software development projects.

IT Service Desk Specialist, CompuCom

APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

I excelled in a high-paced environment, adeptly handling multiple tasks and resolving complex issues, skills directly transferable to the demands of software development. Furthermore, I embraced continuous self-learning and demonstrated my adaptability by taking on team leadership responsibilities.

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Tailwind
- React.js
- Vite
- Git

GitHub

- Self-learner.

SOFT SKILLS

- Adaptability.
- Fast paced.
- Desire to learn.
- Proactive.
- Teamworking.

Ops Supervisor, Qualfon

APRIL 2016 - MAY 2017

Expertise in multitasking, teamwork, self-learning, and fast-paced environments. Skilled in problem-solving and team leadership, driving a successful team's KPI and personal metrics. Effective at managing priorities, fostering collaboration, and adapting to changing circumstances.

EDUCATION

Universidad Autónoma del Estado de

México

AUGUST 2018 - JULY 2024

Academio

MAY 2023 - OCTOBER 2024

Houston Community College JANUARY 2013 – JANUARY 2015